https://www.kvmgalore.com/shopping/privacy.php

Get help
FREE GROUND SHIPPING!
on orders over $99
We specialize in...
IP Central Management
KVM Switches [Single User]
KVM Switches [Multi-User]
Matrix Switches
KVM Switches [Multi-User]
Matrix Video Switches
MultiViewers
MultiView KVM Switches
MultiView Video Switches
Networking [Ethernet]
Audio Switches
KVM Switches [Single User]
Cable KVM Switches
KVM Switches [Multi-User]
Subscribe to KVMGalore
Receive exclusive offers, product updates andpreferred rewards.
Account Login:
KVMGalore® Privacy Policy
KVMGalore® cares about your privacy
At KVM Galore we are dedicated to you, our customer. That's why we take great care to make your online experience with us as private and secure as possible. KVM Galore believes that our customers are our most valuable assets. We recognize that building a long-term business relationship with you depends on earning your trust, and that respecting and protecting your privacy is part of this commitment.
We have designed our website so that, in general, you can explore the information offered without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide personally identifiable information (name, address, email address, phone number.), you can rest assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with KVM Galore.
Please be aware that KVM Galore's privacy practices may vary as required by local laws and policies. Regardless of later updates or changes to our privacy notice, we will never use the information you submit under our current privacy notice in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.
We want you to be informed and aware…
This Online Privacy Statement is provided by KVM Galore in order to make you aware of our privacy practices, and of the choices you can make about how information is collected and used. KVM Galore's Online Privacy Statement is available from our homepage and from every page where information is collected.
KVM Galore pledges to clearly outline the choices you have when you register for a product or service. At the time of registration, you may choose to opt-out of receiving email from KVM Galore about other products or services. You may also exercise your opt-out choice at any time. For additional information, see the Choice/Opt-Out section below.
Security
At KVM Galore, we are committed to ensuring the security of your information. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of info, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
KVM Galore Web site incorporates the most cutting-edge technology in reference to security. All communication pertaining to purchases, or containing personal information are fully secured, using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, to prevent the information from being intercepted. All customer information is kept in data files to which access is limited to only those employees who must use this information to process the order. Access to hard copy paperwork is limited through the use of locked cabinets in our facilities and a security system is also in place to protect our premises.
All employees, agents and affiliates of KVM Galore have who might have access to confidential customer information in the conduct of their duties have agreed to hold this information in confidence, not to use it for any purpose except to carry out the service they are providing for our organization, and to honor our privacy and security policies in the way this information is handled. Under no circumstances will we use this information for anything else not described in this privacy policy.
KVM Galore's Privacy Advocate is responsible for conducting investigations into any alleged computer or network compromises, incidents or problems and ensuring the proper disciplinary action is taken against those who violate KVM Galore's Information Security Policy. Any security compromises or potential security compromises and any inquiries concerning security should be reported to privacy.advocate@kvmgalore.com.
Information Collection
KVM Galore offers our website visitors the opportunity to:
View product information.
Generate quotes.
Purchase products.
We may ask you to provide personal information in order to process these business transactions efficiently. The information you share with KVM Galore will be used to support the customer relationship you have with KVM Galore.
KVM Galore collects visitor information in the following areas:
Generating a quote.
Shopping online.
Depending on the type of transaction you request, you may be asked to provide your name, contact , shipping, and billing information, transaction and credit card information, contact preferences, and email address.
Information Use
KVM Galore uses the information you provide to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to:
Help you complete the desired transaction.
Communicate back to you.
Update you regarding products, services and benefits.
Adapt our website and printed materials to fit your needs.
Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained.
We may also occasionally use your information to contact you for market research or provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. KVM Galore will always give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such contact. In addition, we will also follow local requirements, such as allowing you to opt-in before receiving unsolicited contact, where applicable.
Contact information such as products purchased, source of lead, date of first contact and last purchase, and type of information requested, are collected and are linked to personally identifiable information such as name and address in our database. This information is analyzed in a consolidated form to determine future product and advertising initiatives to best serve our customers. Analysis of individual buying behavior may be utilized to grant discounts, or extend lines of credit.
In the event that product ordered by our customer gets drop-shipped directly from the manufacturer, only information that is needed to ship an order will be shared with that manufacturer. The information shared with such manufacturer does not include sensitive information such as credit card numbers, credit information, medical information, social security numbers or other related information, nor does it include personally identifiable information regarding children.
We may only share aggregate demographic information with our partners and advertisers. Such aggregate demographic information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
KVM Galore will not share, sell, rent, lease, or trade any of your personally identifiable information with any outside party without your explicit consent, unless required by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.
Log Files
IP addresses are used to analyze trends, administer the site and track user's movement within our site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Email Links
We use email links to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments to improve our site and features, or review and discard the information. Your personal information is shared with third parties only with your explicit permission.
Forms, Surveys
Our site may request information from users via form or surveys. Participation is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as email address, name, title, company address, or telephone number). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site, and to communicate with users regarding new products or special offers.
Newsletter and Special Offers
Users who sign up to receive information will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to decline these types of communications.
Site and Service Updates
KVM Galore may send users site and service announcement updates. We may communicate via email with users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts.
Choice/Opt-out
KVM Galore will always provide you the opportunity to at any time let us know if you wish to opt-out of partial or all contact from KVM Galore. This choice may be offered at the bottom of an online or offline communication from us, as well as on many of our web registration pages. If you have any difficulty exercising your choices, please send your request to privacy.advocate@kvmgalore.com
Future use
As KVM Galore develops our business, there may be a change of control of KVM Galore, or subsidiaries, affiliates or portions of KVM Galore. In this situation, customer information is typically considered a transferable asset. Also, in the occurrence that KVM Galore or a part of its divisions, affiliates or subsidiaries are purchased, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.
Notification of Changes
KVM Galore reserves the right to make changes to our online privacy policy as business or technical needs require. In the future, should KVM Galore decide to use the information that you provided in a substantially new way, we would notify you based on the email address you provided and offer you the opportunity to opt out of the new use.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, we would like to know so we can address them. Please contact the privacy.advocate@kvmgalore.com or call 1-800-636-3434.
INFORMATION
About us
FAQ
Order status
Privacy policy
Return policy
Site map
Terms & conditions
Copyright © 2020 KVMGalore® - All rights reserved.
KVMGalore, and the KVMGalore logo are registered trademarks of Rackit® Technology Corporation. Tech Solutions Made Easy is a trademark of KVMGalore®.
All other marks are property of their respective owners.
